(Raj:)You sure?
(Leonard:)Look.
(Howard:)The system is maintaining
its own stability,
(Howard:)the quantum vortex apparatus is
now controlling the orientation.
(inhales)
(Raj:)You're right.
(Raj:)You realize what this means?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)I do.
(Howard:)It's proof of concept.
(Howard:)We've got a
workable guidance system.
(Raj:)Congratulations.
Thanks!
(chuckles)
(computer chimes)
(Leonard:)Hey,
(Howard:)I just got an e-mail
from the U.S. Air Force.
(Raj:)Open it.
(Howard:)Hmm.
"We request a meeting at your
earliest convenience
"regarding your
quantum guidance system,
provisional patent 62/295118."
(Howard:)That's weird.
(Raj:)Is there a window around
here we don't know about?
(Howard:)I'm sure
it's just a coincidence.
(Raj:)Yeah, of course.
(Raj:)What else could it be?
(raised voice):
Boy, do I love America.